In this video, I'm going to give
you some guidance on completing your
presentation software assessment.
At this point, you will have
completed unit one Word Processing
Software and submitted your
assessment to your tutor for marking.
While you're waiting for the tutor
to mark your work, you can then move
on to unit two Presentation Software.
So again, you will work through each
of the sessions within the unit two
and complete the relevant sections
within the unit two assessment.
So, what I'm going to do is I'm just
going to bring up the actual unit two
assessment, and I will access that
and double click on the document.
And that will open up the Word document.
It's structured exactly the same way
as the word processing assessment.
And you will see the learning outcomes
at the top relating to presentations
and improving productivity using IT.
Those are the learning outcomes
that you have to achieve.
You are then given the scenario.
And it's important that you
fully understand what the
scenario is asking you to do.
For part one, this is all about
approaching a task, and this is
primarily a question-based section.
So you need to understand what is being
asked and then answer the questions fully.
And once you've completed these questions,
you then move on to part two, which
is about creating your presentation.
The very first question, our first
task within this section, is about
providing a screen print, showing the
location of the assessment document.
So as with word processing, you just need
to take a screen print of the folder,
containing the assessment document.
So take a screen print of that, and
then paste that into that space there.
I can then move on to the next
question, complete that question.
And then it is time to start
creating the actual presentation.
So follow the instructions carefully
and use the resource files that
you've downloaded to allow you to
create the content and add the various
effects and images that are required.
And then once you've done that, you
would save that as" PS2 presentation".
The next section is primarily about
making changes to that presentation.
So this question here, or this
task here, is very important.
So you need to retrieve the
presentation file and then save
it as "PS2 presentation complete".
So that will then give you two versions.
It's very important because this section
here is all about making changes.
So your tutor will need to see the
PS2 presentation file which was the
document that you created in part two.
And he will then refer to the presentation
complete file to see the actual
changes that you make in this section.
So once you've completed that
there are several questions
that you need to answer again.
Remember the command verb: describe,
explain, outline, identify and
answer the question accordingly.
And once you've completed all of
that, you can then submit your
work to your tutor for assessment,
again, as with word processing,
please make sure that you complete
all three parts of the assessment.
Otherwise your tutor will not
be able to mark your work.